35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing], circa 1970s; 15 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Man standing in front of "Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun"], 2
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Train (monorail?), 3
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Train tracks], 4
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Train tracks], 5
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Train tracks], 6
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Inside of train car (monorail?), 7
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Ski house that reads "Ticket Sales"], 8
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: People sitting at table eating], 9
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: People sitting at table eating], 10
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: People sitting at table eating], 11
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: People sitting at table eating], 12
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: People sitting at table eating, Lowell Thomas at left], 13
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: People sitting at table eating, Lowell Thomas at left], 14
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Four men and Lowell Thomas in the center], 15
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas with another man in front of snowy mountains], 16
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Four men and Lowell Thomas in the center], 17
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas and another man at ski club], 18
    - [Carousel number 2 [golf; Lowell and Frances Thomas; zoo; Colorado Women's College; Will Rogers Shrine of the Sun; skiing]: Lowell Thomas sitting in chair], 19
  - Carousel number 3 [golf], 1954, circa 1973; 16 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas with dog in red golf cart in front of house on golf course], 1
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 2
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Aerial view of golf course], 3
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Aerial view of golf course], 4
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Aerial view of golf course and house], 5
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Aerial view of golf course and house], 6
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Side view of house on golf course], 7
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: People riding in red golf carts], 8
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: People riding in red golf carts], 9
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course], 10
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course], 11
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course], 12
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course], 13
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Trees on golf course], 14
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas riding in red golf cart with their dog], 15
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course and house in the distance], 16
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: View of golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 18
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course (dark picture)], 19
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Side view of house on golf course], 20
  - Carousel number 3 [golf], 1954, circa 1973; 17 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: View of golf course], 1
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: View of estate], 2
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: View of estate], 3
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: View of estate], 4
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: View of golf course], 5
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: View of golf course], 6
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Aerial view of golf course], 7
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Aerial view of golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Side view of house on golf course], 9
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Trees changing colors for autumn], 10
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lake and changing trees for autumn], 11
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 12
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Aerial view of estate on golf course], 13
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 14
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas in red golf cart with their dog], 15
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: House on golf course hidden by trees], 16
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course (dark picture)], 17
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell and Frances Ryan Thomas's dog among the trees], 18
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Little white house on golf course], 19
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell and Frances Ryan Thomas's dog among the trees], 20
  - Carousel number 3 [golf], 1954, circa 1973; 18 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Flowers growing on golf course], 1
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course], 2
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course], 3
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Side view of house on golf course], 4
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course], 5
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Backyard of house on golf course; garden and garage], 6
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas golfing (dark picture)], 7
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas golfing (dark picture)], 8
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas in red golf cart], 9
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course during autumn], 10
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 11
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: On golf course, Lowell Thomas at right, another man riding in red golf cart], 12
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 13
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 14
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Lowell Thomas golfing], 15
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course (dark picture)], 16
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: House on golf course], 17
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: River], 18
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Man riding golf cart], 19
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course], 20
  - Carousel number 3 [golf], 1954, circa 1973; 19 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course during autumn], 1
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course during autumn], 2
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course during autumn], 3
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Gravel road winding through forest], 4
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: River], 5
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Red leaf bush], 6
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Road running by golf course], 7
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Road running by golf course], 8
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Road running by golf course], 9
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course during autumn], 10
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course during autumn], 11
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in red golf cart with her dog], 12
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Aerial view of golf course], 13
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course], 14
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Man riding in golf cart], 15
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf course during autumn], 16
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf scorecard signed by Lowell Thomas and others (illegible)], 17
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf scorecard signed by Lowell Thomas and others (illegible)], 18
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf scorecard signed by Lowell Thomas and others (illegible)], 19
    - [Carousel number 3 [golf]: Golf scorecard signed by Lowell Thomas and others (illegible)], 20
  - Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas], 1973, circa 1970s; 20 (Box 1583)
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas standing with an officer in front of window that reads "Cripple Creek Gold Rush. A Weekly Newspaper Attempting Business in Teller County], 1
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas standing next to sign that reads "Victor Colo. City of Gold. Mines Elev. 9717"], 2
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas standing with another man next to a train], 3
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas standing in front of old photos], 4
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas standing in front of poster for "Allenby in Palestine and Lawrence in Arabia"], 5
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas standing in a room], 6
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas with another man looking through newspapers], 7
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas at printing press], 8
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in a restaurant with a police officer, another man, and woman], 9
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas pouring alcohol behind the bar of a restaurant with another man], 10
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas at printing press], 11
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas standing in an office], 12
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Stairs], 13
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: House], 14
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Entrance to neighborhood, palm trees], 15
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas in wheelchair, and another woman standing on cobble stone road], 16
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in wheelchair holding purse], 17
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: View of snowy mountains], 18
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas sitting (in ski lift?)], 19
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas with Frances Ryan Thomas and another woman on road surrounded by red rock], 20
  Box 1584
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 4 (continued from previous box) [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas], 1973, circa 1970s; 1 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Sign that reads "If you'd have mind at peace, a heart that cannot harden - go find a door that opens wide upon a lovely garden. Welcome to Cypress Gardens"], 1
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People watching a person dressed in a tiger costume], 2
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas standing on a road surrounded by red rock], 3
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Motorboat speeding by with wakeboarders], 4
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Wakeboarders riding by holding flags that spell out "(?) Lowell"], 5
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas standing on a road surrounded by red rock], 6
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Woman looking over at view of the ocean from balcony of resort], 7
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: View of flower garden], 8
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Boats on water], 9
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Woman looking at view from balcony of resort], 10
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Sun setting over the horizon, palm trees], 11
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Young lady with Frances Ryan Thomas, sitting beside the pool of resort], 12
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Giraffe walking on road], 13
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Giraffe walking on road], 14
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in wheelchair], 15
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Palm trees and neighborhood ahead], 16
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Young girl standing beside a sign that reads "Trespassers will be eaten"], 17
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas looking over balcony of resort], 18
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas reading newspaper, Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in wheelchair], 19
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Cars on road], 20
  - Carousel number 4 (continued from previous box) [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas], 1973, circa 1970s; 2 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Frances Ryan Thoams sitting in wheelchair, Lowell Thomas and another woman beside her in front of statue], 1
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Young girl lying on couch], 2
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Frances Ryan Thomas with another woman, looking at the elephants], 3
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Jet taking off runway], 4
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas in front of statue ], 5
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas next to an alpaca], 6
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Frances Ryan Thomas looking at lions though the window of the car], 7
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas in front of statue], 8
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Pile of wood], 9
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas reading newspaper outside, another woman sitting next to him], 10
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas reading newspaper outside], 11
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lawn chairs and palm trees], 12
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas and another man standing next to an alpaca], 13
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas and another man standing next to an alpaca], 14
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas standing with another man, both in suits], 15
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Girl sitting on an alpaca], 16
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas sitting on an alpaca], 17
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: View of garden], 18
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas sitting on an alpaca], 19
  - Carousel number 4 (continued from previous box) [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas] [Items 1-12] Carousel number 5 [Items 13-20], 1973, circa 1970s; 3 (Box 1584)
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People sitting around dining table], 1
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People seated at dining tables], 2
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People seated at dining tables], 3
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People seated at dining tables], 4
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People seated at dining tables, Lowell Thomas at left], 5
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People seated at dining tables], 6
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People sitting around a round table, Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas at the right], 7
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People seated at dining table], 8
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People sitting at dining tables], 9
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas riding in a golf cart], 10
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: Lowell Thomas standing, wearign a suit], 11
    - [Carousel number 4 [Cripple Creek/Victor, Colorado (1973); Utah; Florida; Lake Mead; Las Vegas]: People seated at dining table, Frances Ryan Thomas at left], 12
    - [Beginning of Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas riding in a red golf cart], 13
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in golf cart with their dog], 14
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas riding in a golf cart], 15
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas riding in a golf cart], 16
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas riding in a golf cart], 17
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas riding in a golf cart], 18
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in a golf cart with their dog, young girl standing beside them], 19
    - [Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas riding in a golf cart], 20
  - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous], 1949, circa 1970s; 4 (Box 1584)
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: The Potala Palace], 1
    - Carousel number 5 [Tibet-3 slides (1949); golf with Lowell and Frances Thomas; family gathering; Lowell Thomas and Richard Nixon; Oral Roberts in Alaska; Lowell Thomas broadcasting; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas riding in a red golf cart], 2